Then how can they speak English without any errors?
كيف يمكنهم التحدث باللغة الإنجليزية دون أي أخطاء؟
Native speakers learn most of their grammar without realizing it.
يتعلم المتحدثون الأصليون معظم قواعدهم دون أن يدركوا ذلك.
It comes naturally to us when we talk and listen.
يأتي ذلك بشكل طبيعي لنا عندما نتحدث ونستمع.
Doesn't that apply to your native language?
ألا ينطبق ذلك على لغتك الأم؟
Then why do you think you can learn English by memorizing grammar rules?
لماذا تعتقد أنك تستطيع تعلم الإنجليزية من خلال حفظ قواعد النحو؟
Here the place has changed to care for, to learn any language.
هنا المكان قد تغير ليهتم، ليتعلم أي لغة.
You need to surround yourself with people who know the language well.
يجب أن تحيط نفسك بأشخاص يعرفون اللغة جيدًا.
Pingo learn app lets you practice everyday
تطبيق بينغو ليرن يتيح لك الممارسة كل يوم.
English expressions in real life situations.
تعبيرات إنجليزية في مواقف الحياة الواقعية.
In one lesson, you will go grocery shopping in English
في درس واحد، ستذهب للتسوق في السوبرماركت باللغة الإنجليزية.
and another lesson you will be asked to order coffee in English.
وفي درس آخر ستُطلب منك طلب القهوة باللغة الإنجليزية.
Remember, English can only be learned by speaking it.
تذكر، يمكن تعلم اللغة الإنجليزية فقط من خلال التحدث بها.